Hello, Sam. Come in.
你好，萨姆。进来吧。
Hi, Sam.
你好，萨姆。
We're having lunch.
我们正在吃午饭，
Do you want to have lunch with us?
你跟我们一起吃午饭好吗？
No, thank you, Tom.
不，汤姆，谢谢。
I've already had lunch.
我已经吃过饭了。
I had lunch at half past twelve.
我在12点半吃的。
Have a cup of coffee then.
那么喝杯咖啡吧。
I've just had a cup, thank you.
我刚喝了一杯，谢谢。
I had one after my lunch.
我是在饭后喝的。
Let's go into the living room, Carol.
我们到客厅里去吧，卡罗尔。
We can have our coffee there.
我们可以在那里喝咖啡。
Excuse the mess, Sam.
屋子很乱，请原谅，萨姆。
This room's very untidy.
房间里乱七八糟。
We're packing our suitcases.
我们正在收拾手提箱。
We're going to leave tomorrow.
明天我们就要走了。
Tom and I are going to have a holiday.
我和汤姆准备去度假。
Aren't you lucky!
你们真幸运！
When are you going to have a holiday, Sam?
萨姆，你准备什么时候去度假？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I've already had my holiday this year.
今年我已度过假了。
Where did you go?
你去哪儿了？
I stayed at home!
我呆在这里了！